<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi there! on Orvin Demsy</title>
    <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hi there! on Orvin Demsy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://orvindemsy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Tranfer Learning on MI-based BCI</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>Description will be updated soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Grid Search/Randomized CV’s (refit=True)</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/blog/blog-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/blog/blog-3/</guid>
      <description>In this article I will share my experience and knowledge of implementing hyperparameter tuning with scikit-learn’s GridSearchCV or RandomizedCV. Concretely, I will focus on refit=True parameter as those are the ones that confuses me the most upon early use of GridSearch/RandomizedCV. I hope this article will help you build better understanding on those methods Pre-requisite First off, as prerequisite a basic understanding in the following topics are expected:
 K-Fold CV Training a model Hyperparameters  I will try to explain briefly here, but I encourage you to read up information about it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filter-Bank Common Spatial Pattern</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Filter-Bank Common Spatial Pattern is a modification of CSP where raw EEG signal is being bandpass-filtered with 9 specific bands (0-4Hz, 4-8Hz, 8-12Hz, &amp;hellip; 36-40 Hz) before CSP is applied on each filtered EEG band.
This work will implement FBCSP on BCI Compeition Dataset 2a. This work will only classify two class, i.e. right and left hand imagery out of total four class.
Early result on three subjects shows FBCSP gives better accuracy than CSP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KL divergence on iris dataset</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/blog/blog-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/blog/blog-2/</guid>
      <description>KL Divergence on Multivariate Gaussian (Example on Iris Dataset) I was doing research in brain-computer interface and was interested in in the technique of transfer learning. Based on numerous papers I read, KL-divergence is a common method to measure similarity of distribution between subjects. At that time, I found an article that explained KL divergence to measure similarity on data with one variable [1]. But I could not find example KL divergence on multivariate data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Two-Class BCI Motor Imagery Display</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>This program serves as interface for two-class BCI motor imagery application. Two major programs are used in this application, the first one is the GUI program which is built in python language. Second one is the program that interacts with g.tec USB AMP device to record EEG signal. This one is an exe application generated by program written in C#. In this document the first program (GUI) may be referred as ‘master’, while the second one (recording) is referred as ‘slave’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Alignment using Euclidean Alignment</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/blog/blog-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/blog/blog-1/</guid>
      <description>Will be updated soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Spatial Pattern</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Brain-computer interface requires several steps in order to work. Among those step are feature extraction. In order to be able to operate BCI system optimally a powerful feature extraction method is required. In motor-imagery (MI) paradigm a commonly used method for feature extarction is called common-spatial pattern (CSP). This is my implementation of CSP algorithm on BCI dataset IV 2a.
Snapshot of classification result   See here to see more about this project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coursera Machine Learning Course</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>This project is a python implementation of Andrew Ng&amp;rsquo;s Machine Learning Course on Coursera, the original course was done in MATLAB.
Although scikit-learn package provide robust functionality to perform machine learning, this code doesn&amp;rsquo;t use it. This work also serves as an exercise for me to learn a python language.
The course syllabus is taught over the span of eleven weeks, the details of each week&amp;rsquo;s topic are as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>https://orvindemsy.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://orvindemsy.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to connect with me, I&amp;rsquo;m available on
         Github www.github.com/orvindemsy   Linkedin www.linkedin.com/in/orvin-demsy    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
